Office of Price Administration
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series II: Regulation Master File, 1941-1946
  - Maximum Price Regulation/Revised Price Schedule/Supplementary Storage Regulation
    - 248 Manganese Ores (Box 7:, Folder 310)
    - 249 Food Products (Box 7:, Folder 311)
    - 250 Food Products (Box 7:, Folder 312)
    - 251 Construction of Buildings and Structures (2) (Box 8:, Folder 313)
    - 252 Vinegar Cures Herring (Box 8:, Folder 314)
    - 253 Softwood Lumber (2) (Box 8:, Folder 315)
    - 254 Small Arms and Parts (Box 8:, Folder 316)
    - 255 Food Products (Box 8:, Folder 317)
    - 256 Food Products (2) (Box 8:, Folder 318)
    - 257 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 8:, Folder 319)
    - 258 Chrome Ores (Box 8:, Folder 320)
    - 259 Malt Beverages (2) (Box 8:, Folder 321)
    - 260 Tobacco (2) (Box 8:, Folder 322)
    - 261 Building Materials (Box 8:, Folder 323)
    - 262 Food Products (2) (Box 8:, Folder 324)
    - 263 Plastics (Box 8:, Folder 325)
    - 264 Protective Coatings (2) (Box 8:, Folder 326)
    - 265 Sales by Canners of Salmon (2) (Box 8:, Folder 327)
    - 266 Certain Tissue Paper Products (2) (Box 8:, Folder 328)
    - 267 Sponges (Box 8:, Folder 329)
    - 268 Food Products (2) (Box 8:, Folder 330)
    - 269 Poultry (3) (Box 8:, Folder 331)
    - 270 Dry Edible Beans (3) (Box 8:, Folder 332)
    - 271 Potatoes & Onions (4) (Box 8:, Folder 333)
    - 272 Building Materials (2) (Box 8:, Folder 334)
    - 273 Apparel (Box 8:, Folder 335)
    - 274 Silk Hosiery (2) (Box 8:, Folder 336)
    - 275 Honey (2) (Box 8:, Folder 337)
    - 276 Asphalt (2) (Box 8:, Folder 338)
    - 277 Mackerel (Box 8:, Folder 339)
    - 278 Totaquina Products (Box 8:, Folder 340)
    - 279 Hops (2) (Box 8:, Folder 341)
    - 280 Food Products (2) (Box 8:, Folder 342)
    - 281 Hardwood Lumber (Box 8:, Folder 343)
    - 282 Chemicals (Box 8:, Folder 344)
    - 283 Tobacco (Box 8:, Folder 345)
    - 284 Western Primary Forest Products (2) (Box 8:, Folder 346)
    - 285 Imported Fresh Bananas (2) (Box 8:, Folder 347)
    - 286 Sausage Products (2) (Box 8:, Folder 348)
    - 287 Apparel (2) (Box 8:, Folder 349)
    - 288 Special Maximum Prices in Alaska (Box 8:, Folder 350)
    - 289 Dairy Products (4) (Box 8:, Folder 351)
    - 290 Sitka Spruce Lumber (2) (Box 8:, Folder 352)
    - 291 Certain Syrups and Molasses (Box 8:, Folder 353)
    - 292 Citrus Fruits (2) (Box 8:, Folder 354)
    - 293 Stock Millwork (2) (Box 8:, Folder 355)
    - 294 Electric Appliances (Box 8:, Folder 356)
    - 295 West Coast Ethyl Alcohol (2) (Box 8:, Folder 357)
    - 296 Flour (2) (Box 8:, Folder 358)
    - 297 Natural Resins (Box 8:, Folder 359)
    - 298 Rotenone and Pyrethrum (Box 8:, Folder 360)
    - 299 Fresh, Cured & Canned Meats (Box 8:, Folder 361)
    - 300 Rubber Drug Sundries (Box 8:, Folder 362)
    - 301 Rubber Drug Sundries (2) (Box 8:, Folder 363)
    - 302 Magnesium Scrap (Box 8:, Folder 364)
    - 303 Frozen Canadian Smelts (Box 8:, Folder 365)
    - 304 Special Utility Shirts (2) (Box 8:, Folder 366)
    - 305 Corn Meal, Corn Flour (2) (Box 8:, Folder 367)
    - 306 Food Products (3) (Box 8:, Folder 368)
    - 307 Waxed Paper (2) (Box 8:, Folder 369)
    - 308 Tobaccos (Box 9:, Folder 370)
    - 309 Platinum (Box 9:, Folder 371)
    - 310 Iron & Steel (2) (Box 9:, Folder 372)
    - 311 Sales by Canners of Shrimp (Box 9:, Folder 373)
    - 312 Food & Food Products (2) (Box 9:, Folder 374)
    - 313 Veneer Logs (2) (Box 9:, Folder 375)
    - 314 Magnesium (Box 9:, Folder 376)
    - 315 Insecticides (Box 9:, Folder 377)
    - 316 Abrasive Products (Box 9:, Folder 378)
    - 317 Locks & Lock Sets (Box 9:, Folder 379)
    - 318 Feathers & Down (Box 9:, Folder 380)
    - 319 Certain Bakery Products (2) (Box 9:, Folder 381)
    - 320 Wooden Containers (2) (Box 9:, Folder 382)
    - 321 Fire Extinguishers (Box 9:, Folder 383)
    - 322 Alfalfa Hay (2) (Box 9:, Folder 384)
    - 323 Asphalt Products (Box 9:, Folder 385)
    - 324 Eastern Fence Posts (2) (Box 9:, Folder 386)
    - 325 Rayon (Box 9:, Folder 387)
    - 326 Macaroni Products (Box 9:, Folder 388)
    - 327 Non-metallic Minerals (Box 9:, Folder 389)
    - 328 Oysters (2) (Box 9:, Folder 390)
    - 329 Food Products (2) (Box 9:, Folder 391)
    - 330 Apparel (2) (Box 9:, Folder 392)
    - 331 Soybeans (Box 9:, Folder 393)
    - 332 Apparel (Box 9:, Folder 394)
    - 333 Eggs & Egg Products (3) (Box 9:, Folder 395)
    - 334 Rabbits (2) (Box 9:, Folder 396)
    - 335 Peanuts & Peanut Butter (2) (Box 9:, Folder 397)
    - 336 Fresh, Cured & Canned Meats (3) (Box 9:, Folder 398)
    - 337 Frozen Lake Smelts (Box 9:, Folder 399)
    - 338 Hardwood Lumber (Box 9:, Folder 400)
    - 339 Women's Rayon Hosiery (2) (Box 9:, Folder 401)
    - 340 Cordage (Box 9:, Folder 402)
    - 341 Motor Vehicles & Equipment (4) (Box 9:, Folder 403)
    - 342 Wooden Containers (Box 9:, Folder 404)
    - 343 Red Herring (Box 9:, Folder 405)
    - 344 New Cotton, Linen (2) (Box 9:, Folder 406)
    - 345 Thermoplastic Scrap (Box 9:, Folder 407)
    - 346 Corn (2) (Box 9:, Folder 408)
    - 347 Mica (2) (Box 9:, Folder 409)
    - 348 Red Cedar Logs (3) (Box 9:, Folder 410)
    - 349 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 9:, Folder 411)
    - 350 Iron & Steel (Box 9:, Folder 412)
    - 351 Ferrous Forgings (2) (Box 9:, Folder 413)
    - 352 Chestnut Extract (Box 9:, Folder 414)
    - 353 Certain Fine Chemicals (Box 9:, Folder 415)
    - 354 Copper Sulfate (2) (Box 9:, Folder 416)
    - 355 Fresh, Cured & Canned Meats (3) (Box 9:, Folder 417)
    - 356 Metal Ores (Box 9:, Folder 418)
    - 357 India Tanned Goatskins (2) (Box 9:, Folder 419)
    - 358 Textile Fabrics (Box 9:, Folder 420)
    - 359 Paper Products (2) (Box 9:, Folder 421)
    - 360 Binder Twine (Box 9:, Folder 422)
    - 361 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 9:, Folder 423)
    - 362 Gelatin (Box 9:, Folder 424)
    - 363 Tobacco (Box 9:, Folder 425)
    - 364 Frozen Fish & Seafood (2) (Box 9:, Folder 426)
    - 365 Matches (2) (Box 9:, Folder 427)
    - 366 Fresh Tuna Fish (2) (Box 9:, Folder 428)
    - 367 Horsemeat (2) (Box 9:, Folder 429)
    - 368 Hardwood Lumber (2) (Box 9:, Folder 430)
    - 369 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 9:, Folder 431)
    - 370 Linseed Oil Meal, Cake (2) (Box 9:, Folder 432)
    - 371 Onion Sets (2) (Box 10:, Folder 433)
    - 372 Used Domestic Washing Machines (Box 10:, Folder 434)
    - 373 Hawaii (4) (Box 10:, Folder 435)
    - 374 Hawaii (Box 10:, Folder 436)
    - 375 Machinery & Equipment (Box 10:, Folder 437)
    - 376 Certain Fresh fruits & Vegetables (2) (Box 10:, Folder 438)
    - 377 Die Castings (Box 10:, Folder 439)
    - 378 Mixed Feeds (2) (Box 10:, Folder 440)
    - 379 Tools Steel Scrap (Box 10:, Folder 441)
    - 380 Used Bedsprings (Box 10:, Folder 442)
    - 381 Softwood Lumber (2) (Box 10:, Folder 443)
    - 382 Glass Containers (2) (Box 10:, Folder 444)
    - 383 Glue Stock (Box 10:, Folder 445)
    - 384 Sales by Processors of Salt Codfish (2) (Box 10:, Folder 446)
    - 385 Military Uniforms (2) (Box 10:, Folder 447)
    - 386 Fertilizers (2) (Box 10:, Folder 448)
    - 387 Wheat (2) (Box 10:, Folder 449)
    - 388 Pulpwood (Box 10:, Folder 450)
    - 389 Ceiling Prices for Sausage Items (2) (Box 10:, Folder 451)
    - 390 Soap & Glycerin (2) (Box 10:, Folder 452)
    - 391 Soap & Glycerin (2) (Box 10:, Folder 453)
    - 392 Packaged Drugs (2) (Box 10:, Folder 454)
    - 393 Packaged Cosmetics (2) (Box 10:, Folder 455)
    - 394 Retail Ceiling Price for Kosher Beef (Box 10:, Folder 456)
    - 395 Virgin Islands (Box 10:, Folder 457)
    - 395A Virgin Islands (Box 10:, Folder 458)
    - 396 Atlantic Sea Herring and Alewives (Box 10:, Folder 459)
    - 397 Flax Seed (2) (Box 10:, Folder 460)
    - 398 Variety of Meats & Edible By-products (2) (Box 10:, Folder 461)
    - 399 New Ice Boxes (Box 10:, Folder 462)
    - 400 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 10:, Folder 463)
    - 401 Certain Corn Products (Box 10:, Folder 464)
    - 402 Softwood Lumber (2) (Box 10:, Folder 465)
    - 403 Rubber & Rubber Products (2) (Box 10:, Folder 466)
    - 404 Potash (Box 10:, Folder 467)
    - 405 Ferro Alloys (2) (Box 10:, Folder 468)
    - 406 Plastic & Synthetic Resins (Box 10:, Folder 469)
    - 407 Ferro Alloys (Box 10:, Folder 470)
    - 408 Brass Mill Products (Box 10:, Folder 471)
    - 409 Frozen Fruits, Berries, etc. (2) (Box 10:, Folder 472)
    - 410 Paper, Paper Products (Box 10:, Folder 473)
    - 411 Reusable Steel Storage Tanks (Box 10:, Folder 474)
    - 412 Softwood Lumber (Box 10:, Folder 475)
    - 413 Building Material (2) (Box 10:, Folder 476)
    - 414 Tire Mileage (Box 10:, Folder 477)
    - 415 Rubber & Products (2) (Box 10:, Folder 478)
    - 416 Basic Refractory Products (Box 10:, Folder 479)
    - 417 Feed Screenings (2) (Box 10:, Folder 480)
    - 418 Fresh Fish & Seafood (2) (Box 10:, Folder 481)
    - 419 Sun-dried Shrimp (Box 10:, Folder 482)
    - 420 Shoes & Shoe Findings (2) (Box 10:, Folder 483)
    - 421 Food & Food Products (2) (Box 10:, Folder 484)
    - 422 Food & Food Products (3) (Box 10:, Folder 485)
    - 423 Food & Food Products (3) (Box 10:, Folder 486)
    - 424 Wooden Containers (2) (Box 10:, Folder 487)
    - 425 Fresh Fruits & Berries for Processing (2) (Box 10:, Folder 488)
    - 426 Fresh Fruits & Vegetables (4) (Box 10:, Folder 489)
    - 426 Fresh Fruits & Vegetables (4) (Box 11:, Folder 490)
    - 427 Processed Beans (Box 11:, Folder 491)
    - 428 Cider Vinegar (2) (Box 11:, Folder 492)
    - 429 Used Consumer Durables (2) (Box 11:, Folder 493)
    - 430 Radios & Phonographs (Box 11:, Folder 494)
    - 431 Charcoal (2) (Box 11:, Folder 495)
    - 432 Hardwood Lumber (2) (Box 11:, Folder 496)
    - 433 Paper, Paper Products (Box 11:, Folder 497)
    - 434 Wooden Containers (2) (Box 11:, Folder 498)
    - 435 New Bicycle Tires & Tubes (Box 11:, Folder 499)
    - 436 Fuel, Petroleum Gas (3) (Box 11:, Folder 500)
    - 437 Paper, Paper Products (Box 11:, Folder 501)
    - 438 Apparel (2) (Box 11:, Folder 502)
    - 439 Fresh Fish & Seafood (2) (Box 11:, Folder 503)
    - 440 Tobacco (2) (Box 11:, Folder 504)
    - 441 Tobacco (Box 11:, Folder 505)
    - 442 Peanut Oil Meal (2) (Box 11:, Folder 506)
    - 443 Soybean Oil Meal (2) (Box 11:, Folder 507)
    - 444 Cottonseed Oil (2) (Box 11:, Folder 508)
    - 445 Distilled Spirits & Wines (3) (Box 11:, Folder 509)
    - 446 Pine Tar & Pine Tar Oil (Box 11:, Folder 510)
    - 447 Coal Tar (Box 11:, Folder 511)
    - 448 Canned Clams (2) (Box 11:, Folder 512)
    - 449 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 11:, Folder 513)
    - 450 Writing Paper (2) (Box 11:, Folder 514)
    - 451 Book Paper (2) (Box 11:, Folder 515)
    - 452 Automotive Parts (2) (Box 11:, Folder 516)
    - 453 Automotive Parts (2) (Box 11:, Folder 517)
    - 454 Aromatic Red Cedar Lumber (Box 11:, Folder 518)
    - 455 Cabbage Seeds (2) (Box 11:, Folder 519)
    - 456 Alfalfa Meal (2) (Box 11:, Folder 520)
    - 457 Potato Chips (2) (Box 11:, Folder 521)
    - 458 Lumber (2) (Box 11:, Folder 522)
    - 459 Gummed Kraft Sealing Tape (2) (Box 11:, Folder 523)
    - 460 Western Timber (Box 11:, Folder 524)
    - 461 Canned and Preserved Foods (2) (Box 11:, Folder 525)
    - 462 Prepared Flour Mixes (2) (Box 11:, Folder 526)
    - 463 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 11:, Folder 527)
    - 464 Paper, Paper Products (Box 11:, Folder 528)
    - 465 Machinery & Transportation Equipment (Box 11:, Folder 529)
    - 466 Building Materials (Box 11:, Folder 530)
    - 467 Lumber (2) (Box 11:, Folder 531)
    - 468 Broom Corn (2) (Box 11:, Folder 532)
    - 469 Livestock (2) (Box 11:, Folder 533)
    - 470 Fertilizer (Box 11:, Folder 534)
    - 471 Legume & Grass Seeds (2) (Box 11:, Folder 535)
    - 472 Certain Essential Oils (2) (Box 11:, Folder 536)
    - 473 Canned & Preserved Foods (Box 11:, Folder 537)
    - 474 Lanolin (Box 11:, Folder 538)
    - 475 Dried Fruits (2) (Box 11:, Folder 539)
    - 476 Luggage (2) (Box 11:, Folder 540)
    - 477 Rubber & Products (2) (Box 11:, Folder 541)
    - 478 Coated & Combined Fabrics (2) (Box 11:, Folder 542)
    - 479 Food & Food Products (Box 11:, Folder 543)
    - 480 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 11:, Folder 544)
    - 481 Wooden Containers (2) (Box 11:, Folder 545)
    - 482 Dried Apple Skins (Box 11:, Folder 546)
    - 483 Lumber Products (Box 11:, Folder 547)
    - 484 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 11:, Folder 548)
    - 485 Wooden Containers (Box 11:, Folder 549)
    - 486 Oyster & Clam Shells (Box 11:, Folder 550)
    - 487 Wheat (2) (Box 11:, Folder 551)
    - 488 Pickles & Pickled Products (2) (Box 11:, Folder 552)
    - 489 Ferro Alloys (Box 11:, Folder 553)
    - 490 Edible Tree Nuts (2) (Box 11:, Folder 554)
    - 491 Forest Products (2) (Box 11:, Folder 555)
    - 492 Seed Potatoes (2) (Box 11:, Folder 556)
    - 493 Dried & Processed Apples (2) (Box 11:, Folder 557)
    - 494 Tobacco (2) (Box 11:, Folder 558)
    - 495 Food & Food Products (2) (Box 11:, Folder 559)
    - 496 Vegetable Seeds (2) (Box 11:, Folder 560)
    - 497 Antimony Metal (Box 11:, Folder 561)
    - 498 Canned & Preserved Foods (Box 11:, Folder 562)
    - 499 Imported Watches (2) (Box 11:, Folder 563)
    - 500 Tobacco (2) (Box 11:, Folder 564)
    - 501 Lumber Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 565)
    - 502 Popcorn (2) (Box 12:, Folder 566)
    - 503 Commodities & Services (Box 12:, Folder 567)
    - 504 Paper, Paper Products (Box 12:, Folder 568)
    - 505 Fresh Whole Coconuts (2) (Box 12:, Folder 569)
    - 506 Staple Work Gloves (2) (Box 12:, Folder 570)
    - 507 Certain Fresh & Frozen Fish (2) (Box 12:, Folder 571)
    - 508 Textile Fabrics (Box 12:, Folder 572)
    - 509 Canned & Preserved Foods (2) (Box 12:, Folder 573)
    - 510 Fuel (Box 12:, Folder 574)
    - 511 Food & Food Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 575)
    - 512 Iceland Herring (Box 12:, Folder 576)
    - 513 Lumber (Box 12:, Folder 577)
    - 514 Goat Meat (Box 12:, Folder 578)
    - 515 Soybeans (2) (Box 12:, Folder 579)
    - 516 Used Photographic Equipment (2) (Box 12:, Folder 580)
    - 517 Tobacco (2) (Box 12:, Folder 581)
    - 518 Rough Rice (2) (Box 12:, Folder 582)
    - 519 Thermosetting Plastic Laminates (Box 12:, Folder 583)
    - 520 Wooden Containers (Box 12:, Folder 584)
    - 521 Food & Food products (Box 12:, Folder 585)
    - [522 does not exist] (Box 12:, Folder 586)
    - 523 Plastics (2) (Box 12:, Folder 587)
    - 524 Wooden Containers (2) (Box 12:, Folder 588)
    - 525 Lumber Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 589)
    - 526 Food & Food Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 590)
    - 527 Cookers & Heaters (Box 12:, Folder 591)
    - 528 Rubber & Rubber Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 592)
    - 529 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 593)
    - 530 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 594)
    - 531 Tanning Materials (2) (Box 12:, Folder 595)
    - 532 Tobacco (2) (Box 12:, Folder 596)
    - 533-2 Lumber & Lumber Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 597)
    - 533-3 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 598)
    - 533-4 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 599)
    - 533-5 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 600)
    - 533-6 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 601)
    - 534-1 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 602)
    - 534-2 Lumber & Lumber Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 603)
    - 535-1 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 604)
    - 535-2 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 605)
    - 535-3 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 606)
    - 535-4 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 607)
    - 535-5 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 608)
    - 535-6 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 609)
    - 535-7 Lumber & Lumber Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 610)
    - 536 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 12:, Folder 611)
    - 537 Sales by Canners of Fish Flakes (Box 12:, Folder 612)
    - 538 Lumber Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 613)
    - 539A-B-C Commodities & Services (2) (Box 12:, Folder 614)
    - 540 Maximum Prices for Used Automobiles (2) (Box 12:, Folder 615)
    - 541 Furs (2) (Box 12:, Folder 616)
    - 542 Canned Fish & Seafood Items (Box 12:, Folder 617)
    - 543 Chemicals (Box 12:, Folder 618)
    - 544 Building Materials (Box 12:, Folder 619)
    - 545 Food & Food Products (Box 12:, Folder 620)
    - 546 Building Materials (Box 12:, Folder 621)
    - 547 Apparel (2) (Box 12:, Folder 622)
    - 548 Household Furniture (2) (Box 12:, Folder 623)
    - 549 Tobacco (2) (Box 12:, Folder 624)
    - 550 Cured & Smoked Fish (2) (Box 12:, Folder 625)
    - 551 Tanning Materials (Box 12:, Folder 626)
    - 552 Feedings Stuffs (2) (Box 12:, Folder 627)
    - 553 Furs (Box 12:, Folder 628)
    - 554 Lumber (Box 12:, Folder 629)
    - 555 Lumber (Box 12:, Folder 630)
    - 556 Lumber (Box 12:, Folder 631)
    - 557 Dries Prunes & Raisins (2) (Box 12:, Folder 632)
    - 558 Lumber (Box 12:, Folder 633)
    - 559 Lumber (Box 12:, Folder 634)
    - 560 Lumber (2) (Box 12:, Folder 635)
    - 561 Gum Turpentine (Box 12:, Folder 636)
    - 562 Popcorn Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 637)
    - 563 Glue Stock (Box 12:, Folder 638)
    - 564 Fountain Pens, etc. (2) (Box 12:, Folder 639)
    - 565 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 640)
    - 566 Transportation (2) (Box 12:, Folder 641)
    - 567 Paper, Paper Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 642)
    - 568 Hardwood Lumber Products (2) (Box 12:, Folder 643)
    - 569 Motor Vehicles & Equipment (2) (Box 12:, Folder 644)
    - 570 Apparel (2) (Box 12:, Folder 645)
    - 571 Rental of Certain Types of Commercial Vehicles (2) (Box 12:, Folder 646)
    - 572 Apparel (2) (Box 12:, Folder 647)
    - 573 Soybeans (2) (Box 12:, Folder 648)
    - 574 Livestock (2) (Box 12:, Folder 649)
    - 575 Chemicals (Box 12:, Folder 650)
    - 576 Dry Batteries (Box 12:, Folder 651)
    - 577 Ice Cream & Frozen Deserts (2) (Box 12:, Folder 652)
    - 578 Apparel (2) (Box 12:, Folder 653)
    - 579 Fresh & Frozen Fish & Seafood (2) (Box 12:, Folder 654)
    - 580 Ceiling Prices for Certain Articles (3) (Box 12:, Folder 655)
    - 581 Industrial Services (2) (Box 13:, Folder 656)
    - 582 Food & Food Products (2) (Box 13:, Folder 657)
    - 583 Fabricated Non-dwelling Structures (2) (Box 13:, Folder 658)
    - 584 Personal & Household Accessories (2) (Box 13:, Folder 659)
    - 585 Food & Food Products (2) (Box 13:, Folder 660)
    - 586 Storage & Terminal Services (2) (Box 13:, Folder 661)
    - 587 Canned Fish & Seafood (Box 13:, Folder 662)
    - 588 Food & Food Products (2) (Box 13:, Folder 663)
    - 589 Softwood Lumber Products (2) (Box 13:, Folder 664)
    - 590 Commodities & Services (2) (Box 13:, Folder 665)
    - 591 Building Materials (2) (Box 13:, Folder 666)
    - 592 Building Materials (2) (Box 13:, Folder 667)
    - 593 Wooden Containers (Box 13:, Folder 668)
    - 594 Motor Vehicles & Equipment (3) (Box 13:, Folder 669)
    - 595 Textile Fabrics (Box 13:, Folder 670)
    - 596 Office & Store Machines (2) (Box 13:, Folder 671)
    - 597 Chemicals (2) (Box 13:, Folder 672)
    - 598 Mechanical Refrigerators (2) (Box 13:, Folder 673)
    - 599 Auto Radios (2) (Box 13:, Folder 674)
    - 600 Soybeans (2) (Box 13:, Folder 675)
    - 601 Lumber Products (2) (Box 13:, Folder 676)
    - 602 Women's Nylon Hosiery (2) (Box 13:, Folder 677)
    - 603 Lumber Products (Box 13:, Folder 678)
    - 604 Rye (2) (Box 13:, Folder 679)
    - 605 Apparel (2) (Box 13:, Folder 680)
    - 606 Prefabricated Dwellings (2) (Box 13:, Folder 681)
    - 607 Apparel (2) (Box 13:, Folder 682)
    - 608 Lumber & Lumber Products (Box 13:, Folder 683)
    - 609 Soybeans (2) (Box 13:, Folder 684)
    - 610 Automobiles (2) (Box 13:, Folder 685)
    - 611 Hardwood Lumber (Box 13:, Folder 686)
    - 612 Food & Food Products (Box 13:, Folder 687)
    - 613 Food & Food Products (2) (Box 13:, Folder 688)
    - 614 Hardware (Box 13:, Folder 689)
    - 615 Candy (Box 13:, Folder 690)
    - General Teletypes (3) (Box 13:, Folder 691)
    - List of Active Price Forms, March 15, 1944 (Box 13:, Folder 692)
    - Public Reporting Forms (Box 13:, Folder 693)
    - Price Panel News (8) (Box 13:, Folder 694)
    - Price Panel Review (Box 13:, Folder 695)
    - Second Rev. Maximum Export Price Regulation (3) (Box 13:, Folder 696)
    - Third Rev. Maximum Export Price Regulation (Box 13:, Folder 697)
    - Maximum Import Price Regulation (2) (Box 13:, Folder 698)
    - GMPR [General Maximum Price Regulation] (4) (Box 13:, Folder 699)
  - Supplementary Regulation
    - SR Collation (Box 14:, Folder 700)
    - 1-2 (Box 14:, Folder 701-704)
    - Supplementary Storage Regulations 1 and 2 (Box 14:, Folder 705)
    - 4 (Box 14:, Folder 706)
    - 4 Rev. (Box 14:, Folder 707)
    - 7 (Box 14:, Folder 708)
    - 9 (Box 14:, Folder 709)
    - 11-15 (Box 14:, Folder 710-740)
  - Supplementary Order
    - 5-6 (Box 14:, Folder 741-743)
    - 8-15 (Box 14:, Folder 744-758)
    - 17-32 (Box 14:, Folder 759-780)
    - 34-114 (Box 14:, Folder 781-886)
    - 115-125 (Box 15:, Folder 887-1004)
    - 126 Certain Silk Apparel (3) (Box 15:, Folder 1005)
    - 127-161 (Box 15:, Folder 1006-1051)
    - 162 Footwear (2) (Box 15:, Folder 1052)
    - 163-64 Fluid Milk & Cream (Box 15:, Folder 1053)
    - 165 Imported Hides & Skins (Box 15:, Folder 1054)
    - 166-193 (Box 15:, Folder 1055-1089)
    - General File Interpretations (2) (Box 15:, Folder 1090)
    - Compensatory Adjustment Regulation #1 (Box 15:, Folder 1091)
    - Office of Economic Stabilization Regulation #1 (Box 15:, Folder 1092)
      - Grading and Grade Labeling (3) (Box 15:, Folder 1093)
    - Margin Requirement Regulation #1 (Box 15:, Folder 1094)
- Series III: Handbooks and Manuals, 1942-1951
  - Price Control Handbook (4 v.) (Box 16)
  - Price Operating Procedures (2 notebooks)
  - General Standards for Setting Prices (notebook)
  - Supplementary Regulations to the General Maximum Price Regulation, 1942 (Box 17)
  - 1st Quarterly Report, 1942
  - 2nd Report of the Office of Price Administration, 1942
  - 3rd Report of the Office of Price Administration, 1943
  - 8th Report of the Office of Price Administration, 1944
  - 11th Report of the Office of Price Administration, 1945
  - 16th Report of the Office of Price Administration, 1946
  - 17th Report of the Office of Price Administration, 1946
  - General Ceiling Price Regulations [Economic Stabilization Agency], 1951
  - Battle Stations for All, 1943 (Box 18)
  - “The Attack on Price Control”, 1944
  - Economic Problems of the Reconversion Period, 1944
    [House Special Committee on Post-War Economic Policy and Planning]
  - Renewal of the Price Control Act, 1944
  - Price Control, 1945 December
  - Directory of Commodities and Services, 1945
  - Supplement to Director of Commodities and Services, 1946
  - Directory of Decontrolled Commodities, 1946
  - Price Control Laws and Executive Orders, 1944
- Series IV: Desk Books, undated
  - General Desk Book (4 v.) (Box 19)
  - Commodity Desk Books (Box 20)
    - Building Materials (2 v.)
    - Chemicals and Rubber (2 v.)
    - Consumer Goods (2 v.)
    - Consumer Goods (1 v.) (Box 21)
    - Food (5 v.)
    - Fuel (1 v.) (Box 22)
    - Lumber (2 v.)
    - Metals and Machinery (3 v.)
  - Opinions and Decisions (v. 1-3, 5, index) (Box 23)
- Series V: Posters and Propaganda, undated, 1941-1943
  - “Any Bonds Today?”, 1941 (Box 24:, Folder 1095)
  - Bond materials, undated (Box 24:, Folder 1096)
  - Bond materials, defense, 1941 (Box 24:, Folder 1097)
    - Receipt book, undated (Box 24:, Folder 1098)
  - Bond materials, war
    - Informational, 1942 (Box 24:, Folder 1099)
    - Order forms, 1942-1943 (Box 24:, Folder 1100)
    - Promotional, 1942-1943 (Box 24:, Folder 1101)
  - “Dollars in the War”, 1942 (Box 24:, Folder 1102)
  - “Every Penny Counts” [4 radio scripts], undated (Box 24:, Folder 1103)
  - “Facts About the United Nations”, 1943 (Box 24:, Folder 1104)